All right, positioning.
Evet konumlandırma.
So this is what we have right now and
Şimdiki durum bu şekilde ve
like I said before, for the most part things are in the right place.
daha önce söylediğim gibi çoğu şey yerli yerinde.
The image seems to be pretty much centered in the screen,
Resim neredeyse ekranın ortasında gözüküyor,
happy birthday is in the upper-left corner.
"happy birthday" sol üst köşede.
Really, the only thing that's an issue is that From Lyla is
Problem oluşturan tek şey "From Lyla"
not in the correct place.
doğru yerde değil.
It should be in the lower-right hand corner.
Sağ aşağı köşede olmalıydı.
You can see here at our goal, we've managed to move it down here.
Hedeflediğimiz gibi burada aşağı taşımayı başardık.
Let's go ahead and fix this and turn it into this.
Bunu düzeltelim bu şekle sokalım.
To start, select the attribute or attributes that you need to position
Başlangıç olarak "From Lyla" yazısını ekranda
Namely the lower left-hand corner.
Sağ aşağı köşeye.
Here's a list of attributes and you can go ahead and
Burada özellikler listesi var devam edip
check next to the ones that you think you need.
ihtiyacınız olacak olanları işaretleyin.
Once you've done that, submit your answer to see if it's correct.
Bunu yaptıktan sonra gönderin doğru mu yanlış mı görün.
Once you know the correct attributes to use, open up your code and
Hangi özellikleri kullanacağınızı öğrendiğinizde, kodunuzu açıp
go ahead and add those attributes to the From Lyla text view.
"From Lyla" TextView'ine bu özellikleri ekleyin.